

### Licence



SIA Door Supervisor Licence 1012174439953732

## **Screening questions**

- I have a valid ID (passport or driving licence)
- I have utility bills in my name on the current address
- I have never been convicted of a criminal offence
- I have never been bankrupt in the past
- I don't have any CCJS (County Court Judgement) issued in the past 6 years

# **Key Skills**

- Good Communication Skills.
- Work under pressure with little or no supervision.
- Good interpersonal Relationship with others.
- Maintained a patient and professional demeanor in challenging situations.
- Basic knowledge use in Microsoft words, Microsoft Excel.
- Ability to respond to problems swiftly and analyze situations to make sound decisions.

# **Omotayo Olalekan Shittu**

O Derby, UK

#### E-mail:

shittuomotayo1978@gmail.com

# Summary

I am hardworking, dedicated and knowledgeable with sufficient experience in construction, security, health and safety with administrative skills. My interest in working has evolved through previous roles in both office setting and site. I am diligent and willing to go the extra mile to get the job done. I have a strong attention to details, can work independently and take initiative when necessary.

#### Phone:

07780884957

## **Experience**

### Warehouse operative

Staffline Recruitment Ltd derby uk

- Locating and packaging of goods as per customer orders using bar codes and serial
- Using warehouse machinery to move goods from storage areas to packaging areas.
- Using industrial packaging materials such as cardboard boxes, wooden pallets and bubble wrap safely and securely package goods.
- Ensuring that storage areas are kept fully always stocked.
- Following health and safety policies and procedures in the warehouse.
- Receive and check incoming pick tickets.
- Re-stock inventory manually or with warehouse equipment.
- Adhere to health and safety policies and quality standards

#### **Business/Project Administrator**

Harbidare Consult Ltd Lagos, Nigeria

- Led a team of over 30 workers daily at various sites.
- Established work schedules and assignments for employees.
- Collaborating with Client representatives, architects, engineers and subcontractors to ensure project success.
- Ensuring the Timely completion of Projects.
- Be Responsible for the Day to day running of Projects Sites.
- Preparation of Daily and weekly reports to the office.
- Conduct site inspection and supervision to ensure compliance with safety regulations and company polices.

Oct 2023 - Present

May 2021 - Jul 2023

### Hobbies

Reading, Travelling, Football and Meeting People

### Security Officer.

Tumrad Business Technology Ltd Lagos, Nigeria

- Provide a visible and reassuring presence to deter potential security threats.
- Assisted in the development and implementation of security protocols and procedures.
- Assist with access control by checking identification and credentials of personnel and visitors.
- De-escalate multiple potential violent altercations.
- Performed security checks on 200+ vehicles to identify unauthorized items and prevent theft and vandalism.
- Provide excellent customer services by assisting visitors, employees and clients with inquiries and directions.

### **Education**

Fire marshal

**High Speed Training** 

**Door Security Supervisor** 

Get Licensed

**CSCS** operative

Construction Skills Certification Scheme

Health and safety within a construction environment.

Highfield

**Banksman/Traffic Marshall** 

**High Speed Training** 

**HS&E Test for Operatives** 

CITB

**Emergency First Aid at Work** 

Get Licensed

**ACT AWARENESS** 

Get Licensed

**ACT SECURITY** 

Get Licensed

Jan 2024 - Jan 2024

Oct 2016 - Apr 2021

Jan 2024 - Jan 2024

Sep 2023 - Sep 2023

Jan 2024 - Jan 2024

Dec 2023 - Dec 2023

Sep 2023 - Sep 2023

Sep 2023 - Sep 2023

Sep 2023 - Jan 2024

Sep 2023 - Jan 2024